by H.
Thank you for watching
me
A child like this
me The second half of the quiz showdown between 4th and 5th term students who are still unknown to the public.
If you can answer correctly with less information than the three clues given by Kaban, you will get a high score.
Last time, Kimura's team unexpectedly took the lead.
Don't miss out on tonight's super-turbulence!
Have you ever seen such a girl?
Question 2
The first information is that he knows a lot about whales.
By the way...
She got interested in whales, looked them up, and fell in love with them.
This is hard.
If you remember talking about whales, even a little bit...
That's great.
If he remembers talking about whales...
What do you say, Mr. Kimura? You want to go?
I don't know what "go" means.
Let's leave everyone out of this turn.
Go to the next clue.
Instead of "thank you," say "avocado.
What the hell is that?
I think it's called an avocado.
I guess it's within the motive.
I bet he wouldn't say it if he was a senior.
Or to Mr. Kimura, "avocado.
Bad word.
It's a bad word.
I know the answer to this one.
I narrowed it down to a few people.
Were you right?
You were right.
Look at the members.
Is that what you're saying?
You're paying attention to them, and I'm paying attention to you.
That's why I got it on the first one.
I'd rather go to the whale.
I won't go back.
Three points is good.
Mr. Kimura?
I'll go for him.
If he takes it, it's too risky.
He'll take it.
Strong, strong!
I'll take it. It's okay, as long as it's the same sex.
I'm going to pull it out.
I'm going to draw! When you draw a picture, it's not like you drew a whale.
I wonder if I'm right.
You're right...
Nice try... I never say "persimmon avocado".
But just once, tell Mayu-tan to say "orikagoto" all the time.
Thank you, Joyman.
So, to the last clue with one point for two teams!
I bring a homemade lunch box to the site.
I have a feeling this is it.
You really don't know anything about this, Mayu-chan.
You're totally out of focus.
Is it a proper bento?
Nigiri rice?
Is it a rice ball?
There's no other clue.
The third term team could not come up with a definitive answer.
Did they come up with the correct answer?
I filled in the blanks.
Yumiki
I have an image that she cooks and makes lunch boxes.
I think she'd say something like avocado with "thank you.
It's Yumiki.
It was Yumiki.
She got me.
Nagi-chan.
I brought blueberries in a soup jar to a previous site.
She brought frozen blueberries.
I thought she had such a thing.
She said she eats homemade o-hagi, so it's possible.
I see.
He's also a painter.
He draws whales, too.
Avocado.
I don't think he'll tell me.
Now, is there a correct answer among these two?
The correct answer is Nagi Inoue.
Wow!
Oh no!
There's one point!
I must have looked up whale in the English case, so I'm going to guess Inoue or Kaki.
My Kaki was surprisingly close.My persimmon was surprisingly close.
You know, you know a lot about whales.
I'm sorry, but it's not a picture.
It's not a picture, it's not a picture.
I saw the news about whales, and I thought, "What is it?" and I started looking into it, and it was interesting, and I got hooked.
Heh.
The last time you cooked bento, it didn't look very good.
That's right.
I'm embarrassed that I think it's a normal site.
I'm embarrassed to think that I'm just a regular guy... on a job site with only a few people.
I bring my own food and eat it.
I eat by myself.
What?
You're doing it right.
If you look at the menu, I can make it.
I see... if you do it right.
The way he took the picture is amazing!
What's this?
It's an omelet with cod roe inside!
The kimpira is so delicious!
Amazing!
And avocado!
You don't say avocado!
Something Satsuki told me.
One day, she called me and asked me to send her a picture.
Only avocados came out of nowhere.
And after that, she said "avocado" directly to me twice...
Oh, he says this kind of thing?
Yes, they say it unexpectedly.
He makes silly puns and stuff like that.
LOL!
It's okay to pronounce it like that.
But it has a beginning, too.
Thank you for the avocado.
That's why you see Yamashita here.
I'm home, Omosu!
Mr. Hyoran, my home is...
Cute
May I ask you to do something about the way your wife says that?
Ma'am, this is for real
Mantohi
I'm home is gone!
Mantohi!
Mama mama mama mama mama mama mama mama mama mama mama
Mama mama mama mama mama mama mama mama mama mama
Mantohi
No one in the big pylon has Kay one in the best place.
Any of these kids?
Question 3
I don't actually like dogs or cats.
I don't like dogs or cats.
What a great piece of information!
I don't know why people don't say this nowadays.
By the way, I'm often asked if I'm a dog person or a cat person.
They don't like either one in particular and are at a loss for an answer.
Which one do you like?
Which one do you love the most?
I think she's going to go for it.
Wow!
Five points to the other team for answering that question.
No, we have to go.
Ume Yamashita is a slouch.
I won't, I won't, I won't.
Don't do it... choice.
Yamashita.
That's not Yamashita.
It's Yamashita, right?
Yay!
What do you mean?
It was a mistake.
Do they look alike?
Let's start with Iwakubo.
Flip open!
Saya!
You seem confident about this, but why?
We've had that conversation before.
What?
But that's why I'm so lucky to know her.
Saahimura
Kawasaki
I said that in a naive way.
Kawasaki's a little strange, too.
She's an unusual pure girl.
I wonder if I got these two right.
Too bad.
Nice pass.
Why did you look so confident?
Why did you say that?
So Kanagawa, too.So Kanagawa, too.
Actually, I don't like dogs or cats.
It's not the result of being told off.
I didn't say that.
I did.
I used to have a dog.
I love dogs.
You said you didn't like living things.
I don't like living things.
It was a good idea to leave this part out.
Let's go to the second clue.
I'm good at ping-pong.
Ping-pong.
I'm sure you've said that in the past.
I'm sure you've said this in the past, on TV.
I'm sure I did.
I vaguely remember.
That's right.
You're giving out information on number 2, right?
I don't know.
MG Karakuchi.
That wasn't the way to say it.
Let's say it.
If you like the area...
I don't know...
I don't know, it sounds like fun.
It's going to be fast.
I don't know.
I'll leave you with one clue.
Umezawa and Yamashita are ready to play!
What do you think?
Open!
My guess...
We both had a hard time deciding.
Saku-chan
was actually good at ping-pong in the past.
I'm sure she did.
But why did you choose Matsuo?
I don't really like dogs and cats.
I thought you might say that.
Saku-chan said...
Myu is surprisingly independent.
She can do anything.
She's athletic, too.
I'm sorry... if I drop this.
Please.
I don't know if I'm right or wrong.
Number two.
Yes!
The correct answer is...
The correct answer is Saku Endo!
Yay!
What a waste!
You missed two taps.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I figured it out... by playing ping-pong.
I knew it.
I knew it when I won the ping-pong tournament in Takesaka.
So...
If you have that information, why don't you write about it?
It's not on there.
No, no, no...
I'm scared
When I was a little girl, I was overwhelmed by a dog that came woofing and woofing.
I was overwhelmed.
I'm amazing
Check out the power of the Queen of Ping-Pong, Takesaka
Is she really strong?
She's on the level of a hot springs ping-pong player.
Oh...
Kimura-san was No. 1 in Japan in hot spring ping-pong.
That's pretty impressive.
No. 1 in the country in hot spring ping-pong?
Let's go!
Like this.
Why?
You're good!
I can get it back with time to spare.
Oh, no...
Too close, too close!
If I serve it now...
Once it's in?
That's good!
Okay, here we go.
That was amazing!
I haven't seen Tunnels play table tennis before.
That's good.
We're in it now.
Oh, my God.
You look funny.You look funny.
You look funny.
Wow.
That's good.
It worked.
It's good.
Just a little bit.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
Oh, man, I got that serve in there, so it's really strong when I'm on it.
That's tough.
Get a point, Kimura-san, please.
Wow!
That's great.
Amazing!
Super strong!
Wow!
Peas are good!
They're not bad.
No, it's good!
Oh, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
I don't know if I've ever met a girl like this.
Question 4
The first information is that she thinks she's a beckoning cat.
No, I don't understand.
I don't understand what you mean.
He says that when he goes into his store, customers come to him.
I see.
It's not that he looks like a beckoning cat.
It's a birth.
I see.
Well, then...
The first information on the big score is for all teams to go through.
The strategy is to give more clues.
The next information is that arm wrestling is the weakest in the world.
The weakest.
Weakest.
I'm going.
They won't tell us either.
Wait a minute.
Here comes the team, Mr. Himura.
No, we have to go.
But you might miss it.
No, no, no, no, you're right.
But I don't think we should go.
All teams, here we go.
Three points for a win.
Let's bring out the Emaki-bo team.
Yes, sir.
Iyoki!
I see you're here for the arm wrestling.
I've heard that you've never won.
I heard that you've never won a single match.
I see.
I wonder if he's ready.
Yamashita, you're good!
I see...
I heard that from the manager too.
I see. Well, I have it on good authority.
Come on, Himura-san!
What?
Why?
I'm winning so much!
I don't know if I'm right or not.
We did it! We did it!
All teams answered incorrectly and did not get any points!
By the way, the last clue is...
The last information is that the comedians are going to do their favorite gag.
He's going to do a gag?
Who is this?
This is Ayame Tsutsuki.
Oh, wow.
Is it a gag?
I don't think I've ever seen her do a gag.
What kind of gag? By the way...
He did "Let's make it happen" by Futaichi Yoneda.
What's that about?
Can you play it for me?
Let's make sure it works.
Too cute.
What do you know about arm-wrestling?
It's common knowledge that you're not very good at arm wrestling.
You've never won an arm wrestling match?
I've never won.
Is it the same with youki?
Yes, that's right.
Wait a minute, here are two of the weakest.
That's the one.
So, I'd like to have an arm-wrestling match to determine the world's weakest champion.So, here I would like to discuss the arm wrestling world's weakest champion!
Here we go.
Ready, go!
I can't believe I'm doing this.
I can't really feel the heat.
I'm doing it.
This...
What the hell is this?
Drool-drool-drool!
Two of the weakest.
I'll have another chance to decide them next time, but...
Question 5
The first information is flowers.
By the way, they say you can tell if it's going to rain by the smell.
Shall we go or not?
I'm the only one who's here right now, but I'm not going to go through with it.
I'm through.
Again, the first clue was not given by all the teams.
The next information is that you can do Fukuwa Jutsu.
Who knows this?
Let's move here.
Good luck, Himura-san!
I like the flower, it's like a fool's errand.
It's like a Fukuwa Jutsu.
Come on...
I'm on your side, me.
I'm going to play all teams here to win 3 points
Come on, Himura-san!
I'm gonna do the Fukuwa Jutsu.
I'm going to do Fukuwa-jutsu!
Miyu Matsuo
You like Matsuo, I want to shoot with Matsuo.
You did it once with Yuri-chan on the lower side.
I don't know if that's considered Fukuwa-jutsu.
Come on, Iwako.
Miyu Matsuo
I usually imitate Yuri-chan.
That's all I can rely on.
Is there a correct answer here?
Yes, I do.
Three points.
Tamura, please announce the correct answer.
The correct answer is Kaki-Haruka.
Yes!
Wow!
Here it is!
Himura-san got 3 points at once!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Thanks for the oysters!
I'm so happy!
Is this a kaki?
It's me!
What's this?
When I was in junior high... we were on a basketball team.
All the members took off their jackets and put them in a basket.
I sniffed them out and handed them to them.
I remembered his smell.
I remembered.
So you can tell.
And I'm doing Fukuwa-jutsu.
You should have this done by now.
You can talk without moving your mouth while smiling.
That's what I mean.
Then please do it.
I'm Kaki Haruka from Nogizaka46.
Pleased to meet you.
He's so mature!
What's with that?
I thought you'd understand.
But it's not like I'm looking at a Fukuwajutsu.
That's great!
I can get him to talk like a normal person.
If you practice with this, you'll be able to do it.
Yes, that's right.
But you don't move it with your mouth.
That's great.
When did you discover this?
You have to smile a lot, don't you?
When I'm recording comments...
"Hi, I'm Haruka Kaki.
It's so creepy!
But I'm still moving a little, so if I practice more...
I'll be great!
Maybe.
You put your lips like that, don't you?
Bananaman-san says it like that, too.
He's a pro at that.
No one shows their teeth.
It's true, it's the dolls that show their teeth.
It's like you're the one showing your teeth.
After this, there was an unexpected ending.After this, there's a surprise ending.
The correct answer is
Final question
Question 6
The first piece of information is eating a loaf of bread all at once.
What the heck is this?
I wonder if he eats a lot.
Who is this?
Shokichi is smiling, but what is this?
He eats it all at once!
It's an avocado pattern.
Avocado pattern.
All at once!
Now let's see if you want to go here...
I'm not going to go, I'm not going to go.
Still no points for Umezawa and Yamashita.
Bet on the bread...
Come on, Ume Yamashita!
Yamashita! The lone winner!
Come on, Yamashita! Ume team!
Pre-pop!
Sugawara.
Sugawara Shokichi!
Why?
When I see you backstage...
I often think that they eat a lot more than I expected.
If I were a member of this group, I'd probably be the one who eats the most.
For real.
That's the image I have of them.
Let's see.............................
Okay, let's go.
Please, please, please.
Is this right?
Four points.
Well, yeah, but...
Too bad.
I'll definitely have to go back.
Now for the second clue.
The next clue is...
He's sleeping in a costume.
Oh, man.
He eats all the bread at once.
And he's sleeping in a stuffed animal suit.
Oh, man.
This is bad.
If Himuro-san wins...
I wonder if Tamura-san gets the prize.
That's right.
We were a horny duo.
Please don't do that.
The horny duo.
Let's go with both teams.
Let's go to Iwakubo's team.
Yumiki!
I see.
Who is it, Mr. Hino?
Matsuo.
Matsuo's popular.
I've been through a lot today.
But it's Matsuo that eats them all at once.
He wears a costume.
I don't think of him that way.
But if you think about it, he eats everything at once.
Give it to him.
Tamura, I'll leave it to you.
The correct answer is Yumiki.
Yumiki!
Yay!
First, Yumiki, eat the bread all at once.
I'll eat it.
I tear it off and eat it.
First we eat it raw, then the second slice with butter, then the third slice with strawberries, then butter strawberries.
Does that mean we have to bake it properly?
Of course.
You eat so much!
That's amazing!
I've been listening to him a lot lately.
All at once, and he's sleeping in his stuffed animal suit.
Sakaki and Kaki came to my house once.
I went.
What were they wearing?
A full-figured dinosaur monster.
You don't wear a capo.
They all wear capos... once...
Dinosaurs? Dinosaurs? Which one of you is once a momen?
What was the third one, by the way?
The third thing is... the person I admire the most is Cinderella.The third piece of information is that the person I admire the most is Cinderella.
Yay, yay, yay.
I know what I'm talking about.
I've always wondered...
I've always wondered... why do you look up to Cinderella so much... when you're wearing the same outfit?
Because they're opposites. - Opposites of what?
What's the opposite of what?
I know the opposite.
I know the opposite of what you mean.
He's rich.
It says here that he has a book of quotes.
Quotes.
I used to read Cinderella quotes at 6:00 in the morning.
By the way, do you remember any of them?
Don't worry, I have the other one.
It's abrupt.
It's so abrupt.
With two teams tied here, it's time to play for the championship.
Thank you very much.
The first information is that you can make the strongest bangs.
This is said to be the strongest bangs in Nogizaka, and they don't even do victories such as the Jingu Live.
Even at the Jingu concert, the outdoor wind is blowing.
They're already back home, and they're smiling.
I don't get this.
If we don't get Ms. Hirona, we'll lose.
We've got to go.
What do we do?
I won't.
Let's go, Stringer.
Matsuo's the favorite.
Come on!
Matsuo!
Come here!
You're right, the bangs are done nicely.
This is what I mean.
Seriously, this is scary.
Will Matsuo's miracle happen?
The correct answer is...
Let's see, Iwakubo's team!
Mayu
Tamura, here's Tamura.
It's a sure thing.
He's always bragging about it.
He's always bragging about how beautiful his hair was even when it was raining.
Even when it's raining, even when it's raining.
They say I'm the only one who was born with beautiful hair.
You talk like that.
Matsuo doesn't say that.
That's what Matsuo would say.
Maybe he won't.
Come on, Matsuo!
Come on, give me the right answer.
The correct answer is...
I'm Mayuka Tamura.
Yay!
A comeback win!
You were so close, weren't you, Mr. Iwakubo?
By the way, Tamura, what was the clue after this?
After this... you can imitate anything.
That's what Kakki told me.
What?
He's good at imitating fat people.
I see.
Not a celebrity.
It's like imitating that person.
Or someone who cheats when she steps down the stairs.
or a girl who makes a fool of herself.
She's really good at that.
That kind of thing.
I like girls who make a fool of themselves.
They make a fool of themselves.
I saw that.
It's good.
Girls who can pull off a sneer.
Then do a mock scampering girl.
Yes, please.
[fast forward]
[applause]
It's my lucky morning.
[laughter]
No, I know.
You're good at this.
I know, I know, I know.
And that's why he won the championship in an upset!
Yumetokubo
One extra-large pudding for each of us
Get it!
Please enjoy!
The top is ice cream
The bottom is puddingBelow is the pudding
Total weight 2.4 cups
Yum!
Yum! Yum!
Next notice
Nogizaka46 33rd Single to be released!
New Center to be Announced in the Next Program
National Tour Hokkaido Park on Sale at 24 Cars Heart
This is Inoue Nagi.
I've been in love with you for a while now.
But there's something I haven't been able to tell you.
I actually really like whales.
I even bought myself a whale's illustrated book.
By the way, this may be a cliché, but...
I like the chubby whales the best.
Please subscribe to my channel!
Bye bye!
[ED]